# JUAN MANJARRES



0430810534



O Upper Coomera, QLD 4209

Proactive and enthusiastic individual, capable of effective results working independently or in a team environment.

Excellent interpersonal and communication skills, with the ability to articulate analytical information.

Great attention to detail, excellent time management skills and demonstrable experience in managing multiple priorities simultaneously.

Advanced computer skills with the ability to quickly learn new technologies.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Excellent verbal and written communication
- Planning and time management
- Proactive learner
- Strong work ethic and interpersonal skills
- Confident and motivated
- Analytical and Problem solver

**EDUCATION & TRAINING** 

#### 2009

Bachelor of **Business-Marketing UNAB-Colombia** 

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## **DISPATCH OFFICER (March 2021 - Current)** Global Footcare

- Administrative order entry and invoicing
- Processing orders.
- Maintaining inventory records.
- Organizing local, interstate & international freight
- Assist with container unloading and restocking warehouse.

## PASSENGER SERVICE DELIVERY AGENT (LATAM, EMIRATES, AIR NZ) DNATA (May 2018- March 2021)

- Professionally represent LATAM/EMIRATES/NZ Airlines at all times while adhering to the company's policies and procedures.
- Assist guests with the check-in process correctly.
- Provide exceptional customer service.
- Ensure compliance with TIMATIC regulations (travel documents, Passports and Visa's) are maintained.
- Process over the counter payments (extra luggage, seat changes, special requests)
- Maintain Dangerous Goods awareness and compliance.
- Proactively work through disruptions in schedules for the benefit of the customer/company.
- Assist special needs guests.
- Assist with boarding, disembarking and problem-solving where required.
- Software used: Maacs, AIS Connect (Emirates), SABER (LATAM).

# JUAN MANJARRES





O Upper Coomera, QLD 4209

### **SOFTWARE EXPERTISE**

- Starshipit
- Netsuite
- Microsoft Office
- Maacs
- AIS Connect
- SABER
- Crystal
- Nexus

### **RFFFRFNCFS**

#### **DNATA**

Carlos Lamaison Service Delivery Manager 040567854

# Sales Consultant/Education VETA Education Consultancy (Nov 2017 – May 2018)

- Provide professional advice for international students
- Prepare relevant documents for students' applications
- Communicate with education providers to follow up students' applications
- Assist with students' applications and enrolments
- Assist with students' visa application
- Inbound and outbound calls to prospective students, identifying their needs and future goals
- Responding to prospective student enquiries through email, chat, and various other communication methods to assist the enrolment decision making process

## **EVENING OPERATION SUPERVISOR (Part-Time)** CIRKA (Jul 2017 - May 2018)

- Performed rostering / scheduling tasks
- Conducted site inductions and training for all new staff.
- Escalated any issues to Customer Service Manager.
- Implemented Best Practice procedures where necessary i.e. streamline procedures.
- Ensured employees have knowledge of safe work practices and the equipment is maintained in a safe operating condition.
- Organised monthly ordering.
- Dealt with tenants and clients with respect to the proper cleaning, servicing, and functioning of the building.
- Performed quality inspections as required.
- Ensured company environmental practices are known and maintained.
- Software used: Advance MS Office (excel, word, outlook).

## RETAIL SALES ASSISTANT/COMMERCIAL CENTRAL CLEANING SUPPLIES (Jan 2015 – Jul 2017)

- Met and exceeded sales targets set by management.
- Performed over the counter sales/customer service.
- Generated emails/quotations.
- Attended to phone enquiries.
- Strategically displayed merchandising to reinforce the "CCS" brand.
- Assisted with stock ordering and receiving.
- Software used: MS Office, Excel, NEXUS and Crystal.